

ABOUT ME

Diligent graphic designer with 12+ years of work experience in email marketing, e-commerce design, and digital marketing. Currently continuing education in full-stack web development and UX Design. Aiming to gain more experience and proven knowledge of full-stack development, effective web design, and user experience.

SKILLS

Full-Stack Development *HTML/CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB*

Adobe Creative Suite *Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver*

MS Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook

MacOS & WinOS

REFERENCES

Ashley Jernigan

Inbound Marketing Manager | ELEAD CRM Phone: 817.673.0208

Matthew Cole

Senior Graphic Designer | Balfour 972.922.3102

Tabitha Salazar *Creative Director* | *Balfour*254.652.8119

Susie Otto

Full-Stack Developer | Senior Graphic Designer



Phone: 469.867.2067



Email: hello@susieotto.com



Website: www.susieotto.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Graphic Designer

2018 - Present

Iconic Group | Balfour | Dallas, TX

- Led the team on creation of new live-text HTML/CSS email templates to help minimize spam rating and boost open rates.
- Responsible for the design and creation of email, web, and print marketing for several e-commerce websites
- Designed graphics for social media and display ads, as well as graphic elements throughout the websites and homepages for several brands
- · Designed brochures, experiential displays, and program ads
- Photo retouching and composite creation

Senior Graphic Designer

2017-2018

Andra Group | HerRoom.com & HisRoom.com | Dallas, TX

- Started as Marketing Coordinator and promoted to Senior Graphic Designer within 6 months
- Led the team on creation and production of daily emails planned 2 months in advance
- Designed new email and front page templates to cut down production time and showcase product photography
- Designed several digital lookbooks for different themes, departments and brands
- Planned photoshoots with Art Director and buying team and assisted on set with laydown photography and model shoots

Marketing Coordinator

2016-2017

Rising Fall | Dallas, TX

- Manage multiple PR events and marketing projects to promote Rising Fall
- Managing team of freelance content creators and hiring talent to assist in content creation
- Developing and implementing re-branding strategy
- Developing the marketing strategy for new and existing video services
- Oversee implementation of the Marketing strategy including campaigns, events, digital marketing, and Public Relations
- Efforts are instrumental in spreading brand awareness within the local advertising industry after recently re-branding from previous company with 40-year history in Dallas

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development SMU Professional | Dallas, TX

March 2020 - Present

Bachelor of Applied ScienceWestwood College | Fort Worth, TX

Graduated 2008